JPL Prime (A rough port of my complex JPL game which was for the TI-84 Plus (CE) series calculators)
By: TheLastMillennial

Designed on HP Prime G2
HP Prime (original) compatible

**Installation
Send file JPL v1.00.xxx.hpprgm (where xxx is a version number) to your calculator via the HP Connectivity Kit.
If for whatever reason you want to try the old versions of this program, you can find all the versions under the 'old' folder.

**Overview:
JPL is a simple game where you must fly your premade rocket through checkpoints. It has a cool scrolling background that 
mimics stars (You don't need to avoid them), and a boost feature. Enjoy!

**Controls:
*Launch mode:
[<],[>]----------Move your craft left and right
[Plot],[View]----Boost your craft left and right quickly (uses OMS)
[esc]------------Quit

**Contact:
If you enjoyed playing, or want to report any suggestions, bugs, or  undiscovered, large quantaties of phosphorus;
do so at this topic: http://www.hpmuseum.org/forum/thread-12471.html

**Change log:
V.1.00.002
Fixed & updated readme
added scrolling background
added OMS

V.1.00.000
initial upload.
